Dr yoshio Nash the nation's leading
nuclear scientist and Lieutenant General
SEO arisu the chief of intelligence were
then sent to Hiroshima to investigate
what had happened to the city as their
plane approached the city both men would
look out of the window but what they saw
was not what they had expected to see
the general had seen many Cities laid
waste by fire bombings usually there was
smoldering debris smoke from emergency
kitchens and some signs of human
activity but below him stretched a
lifeless desert no smoke no fires
nothing there wasn't a street in
sight with no Landing Strip visible the
pilots turned around and shouted sir
this is supposed to be Hiroshima what
should we do land said the general their
plane eventually touched down with Dr
NASA beginning to study the city almost
immediately however he would come to the
inevitable conclusion an atomic